Hey.
If you wanna live your best creative life,
we gotta talk.
Because the artist within can only emerge
if we strip away the armor.
The protection you built to stay safe.
That's what we're doing here, together.
So if you're a person who wakes up
with a weight already in their chest,
if you feel anxiety, you feel things deeply,
and you're a sensitive person.
You try to create stuff, you work,
but nothing seems to scratch the itch
that really fulfills you.
And you feel like there's a gap between
what you imagine to create
and then what gets created.
And that gap is too big.
You know deep down that you're a butterfly,
and you got all this potential.
But everyone around you, including yourself,
still sees a caterpillar.
And that's frustrating.
You feel like your sensitivity is proof
that you're not enough.
That you're weak. That you're different.
And that you can't do ordinary things
without falling apart.
This is me.
Look, I've always been sensitive.
I've always been scared.
And the moment everything changed for me
was when I stopped running away from that.
And that's kind of like a cliche term, right?
But I did my first public speaking event
in front of 15 of my closest friends.
And what I realized there in the room,
along with everybody,
is that we are all artists.
And our shadows are actually here
to help us express that art.
And that's beautiful.
So my sensitivity, my anxiety,
the feelings that I feel,
were the gifts I hadn't learned to use yet.
So your sensitivity is not a wound.
It is not a weakness.
It is a gift that allows your art
to carry depth and meaning.
If you think of a butterfly,
the butterfly is a caterpillar
for a very long time.
But at a certain point, it realizes
that it needs to go through a metamorphosis.
So it does.
And it spreads its wings.
And now it can fly.
Now it is airborne.
But there's a process to do that.
So just imagine it.
You don't wake up with anxiety anymore.
The weight is gone.
You wake up feeling excited,
like the day has pure potential,
pure possibility for what could be created.
What kind of magical things
can we create today?
That's what the creative life is.
You feel proud of what you're creating.
You feel it means so much to you.
And it's not just something you make
or something to further along your business.
It is a true, authentic expression
of who you are.
Your sensitivity is not a weakness anymore.
It's actually the gift that you carry.
The sensitive antenna that you have
that allows you to make great art.
It's what makes your work extraordinary,
and it allows you to live the life
you came here to live.
Not only that,
you're also impacting people in ways
that even surprise you.
Your creativity and your art serves the world.
People genuinely love you for it,
because it heals them.
And all you did was express
your truth authentically.
You're embodying the inner artist
you always knew was in there.
And that is the highest version of yourself.
You feel proud, right now,
in your own skin.
And it feels like coming home.
If this is resonating with you,
how do we do this?
Well, we start with the nervous system
and the self-image.
We start in the body.
We look at what triggers your nervous system,
and we learn to regulate it.
We train your body to feel safe.
And when we can be safe,
our intelligence can have fun.
That's what creativity is.
And we completely change how we see ourselves
by requalifying the thoughts
that have been reinforcing the caterpillar,
the person we don't wanna be.
We improve the meaning behind our shadows,
because things like sensitivity
actually represent your gifts
of creativity and authenticity.
So we get you to see yourself
no longer as the caterpillar,
but as the butterfly you are becoming
in real time.
If you take away anything
from listening to my voice right now,
it's that you need permission,
and you need honesty.
You're gonna feel a pure permission
in your body to go this path,
to live this type of lifestyle.
And the honesty to finally see yourself,
and how much love you have for creativity,
and to create your best work.
And there's gonna be so much meaning
behind this that it's gonna fuel you.
And this is what fuels the artist.
This is how you access the creative fire,
live your best creative life,
and go through the metamorphosis.
So if any part of you felt like
I was talking to you here,
it's because I really am talking
to an older version of me.
I am you, in a way.
Which is so cool.
I see you.
I know what you're carrying.
And I want you to know that there is a plan,
and you don't have to figure
all of this out alone.
So here's what I want you to do.
Scroll down.
Leave me your name and your email,
and send me a voice note back
answering the two questions below.
Just speak from the heart.
Tell me what living your best creative life
actually looks like,
and tell me what's been stopping you
from doing that.
And as soon as I get your message,
I'm gonna respond.
That's my promise to you.
And I just wanna say thank you,
and cheers to at least beginning
this creative life.
Because this is what fuels me so much.
So the fact that I get to help you
with this too, man, this is a gift.
Anyways, thank you for listening,
and we'll be in touch soon.